[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Speaker 2: Thank you for calling in touch more customer care.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Who am I speaking with today?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Hi, this is Liz Garcia.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Liz Garcia.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, and then Liz, can I have the phone number that I've linked to the account?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Yes, 951-818-0637.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay, and then the email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Liz L-I-Z Garcia, G-A-R-C-I-A period 1969 at ATT.net.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, and how can I help you today, Liz?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Well, I made a purchase, I believe it was a couple days ago, at the Pet Smart in Ontario, California.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And I used the rewards program per a specific reward that is offered there.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It's seven times the points for New Lo products.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And all I bought was NULO, the dog brand, the food, wet and dry.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And I didn't receive the points yet.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It doesn't show up on my rewards program.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I can give you the order number.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It was the one purchase, I believe it was on Friday, the most recent one for $55 and something odd sense.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Together, pay over $50, something like that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: They get 5,000 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: And I'm sorry.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It's supposed to be on the 31st.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I'm not surprised because I know I just had received some funds, so it had to have been Friday.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And yesterday I called because when I did the online pickup and went to the store to pick it up, it didn't show finalized.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So I called the store yesterday and then they finalized the transaction because it did show up as finalized finally, processed or something like that in the app.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And so they did that for me yesterday, but today I'm not showing it as any kind of fulfillment of the rewards program.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It she's seven times the points that won specifically for new little products.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, Liz, I'm going to put you on the group while I look at your account and see what's going on, okay?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Sure, thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Absolutely.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Hi there.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So I do see on my end that I see that it was the offer was placed along with the 5,000 offer.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Sometimes it can take a bit to show up and it might just not show up on your end, but I see that you see that you have being confirmed.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Let me try the exact number.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] You have 10,103 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: That's what should be showing up.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is it because maybe the transaction wasn't completed until Saturday, which was yesterday, that it is saved of 72 hours, so it would be maybe three days from there.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is that a possibility?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Even though I purchased it on Friday, because I did call and she did finalize it, no problem, but that wasn't until yesterday.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So that could be, I do remember reading that because I looked into it a little bit more closely so that I know what I'm working with here.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I could take up the 72 hours, which is three days.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I will have a 10,030 points or 10,300?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: 10,103 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Oh, 103.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yeah, I just remember being 7,000 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And there was other rewards offered with that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So 5 and then 5,000.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So how much would that be in the money and denomination?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Do you have any idea?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So that $1,400 there now, and it's like $2 or something like that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, so I'm going to ask.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] $4 and some change if I'm correct.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Wait, hold on.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Yeah, because it says the new low so the 5,000 points in and of itself is like $10 or something like that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Or $5.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 1,000 points is equal to $2.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay, because yeah, I have $1,400 in my account right now in the rewards program.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So that's true.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] That's correct.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So for every thousand, it's two.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: So $10,000.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: So what would be double?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So $160.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] That would make sense because $5,000 is $10,000, so it's a double each thousand or five.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And then I don't know what it was, the seven times the points of the new product because it depends on how much I spend.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] But the total amount was $55,000, something.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And then it's all new low.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah, so you got 3,000 points from the seven-time offer, and then $5,000 for the, you know, spend this amount.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] You get 5,000 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I think if you spend 15 points, you get 5,000 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: If the new low was seven times the amount of the price?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] How it works?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: So you said it's your $10,000 points and $103.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So you got $8,694 points that day, but in total you have you have 10,103 points in your account, but from that purchase you only had, you only got 8,600.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Oh, you're saying total with my $1,400.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah, yes, I'm like including like everything in total.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I probably should have just, yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: So for $8,000, that's double could be $16.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] The $5,000 is $10.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Roughly.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So for each thousand points or is it $100?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Each thousand point is $2?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Is that how every $1,000 points is $2.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Because I'm a busy status.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: No, that's just base.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah, that's just standard.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] There's different math when you're a busy as well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Just a lot to break down right now.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: But just so I know, I'm going to be getting 8,103 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is that what you're saying?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 8,694 points.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: If you want.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] If you want, Liz, I can email you both of these numbers.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I can email you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] That'd be great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah, that way you'll know exactly how much you're supposed to have.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So I'm going to go ahead and do that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Yes, that would very much appreciate that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It can be broken down in the email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: That's the amount.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] That would be nice.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm going to put you in a three-four while I do that, okay?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Great, thanks.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Hello, Liz.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yes.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Go ahead and sent that email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It says, and I make sure to put it in bold.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It says exactly how much you were supposed you're going sorry, you're supposed to get from that transaction.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And then I also put how much you should have in total that you should see on your account, okay?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Which is in addition to what I have there, the $1,400, something like that?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Correct.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Correct.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] This is just just to make sure that when you look at your account, it says like this exact number, the $10,103.43.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Oh, okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Good, great, great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I appreciate that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: That is very helpful for me.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] No, that was it for now.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Do you have any idea why it wasn't shown on my account?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is it maybe because of the $22?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Because like you said, like the transaction went through later, and then it's like 72 hours after the transaction is complete.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I did notice that, so I'm trying to think maybe it was that it that the transaction may have taken place on Saturday instead.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: That's when they finalized it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm just curious.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] But I appreciate your help.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Thank you very much.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I'll look forward to looking over that email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yes, ma'am.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I really hope that everything goes well for you, okay?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Thanks for calling that smart customer care.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And you have a beautiful day, okay, Liz?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: You too.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You too.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Bye-bye.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Bye-bye.